<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>workout on Crossfit Workouts</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/tags/workout/</link><description>Recent content in workout on Crossfit Workouts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2023, Crossfit Workouts; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:53:46 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/tags/workout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Crossfit Exercises for Beginners</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-exercises-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:53:46 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-exercises-beginners/</guid><description>
Are you new to crossfit? It can be daunting to walk into a box, but don't worry - everyone starts somewhere! Here are 10 exercises for beginners that can get you started on your crossfit journey.
1. Air Squats Air squats are a great way to strengthen your lower body. Start by standing with your feet shoulder-width apart, then bend your knees and lower yourself down as if you're sitting on an imaginary chair.</description></item><item><title>10 Crossfit Workouts for Beginners</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:53:46 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</guid><description>
Crossfit is a high-intensity, constantly varied functional training that is designed to help you achieve an overall level of fitness. It is a full-body workout that includes a variety of movements such as weightlifting, running, rowing, and gymnastics. If you are new to Crossfit, it can be a bit intimidating to jump into a regular class, which is why we have compiled a list of 10 Crossfit workouts that are perfect for beginners.</description></item><item><title>5 Crossfit Workouts to Get You Summer-Ready</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-to-get-you-summer-ready/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:23:05 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-to-get-you-summer-ready/</guid><description>
Summer is right around the corner, and if you're looking to get into shape, Crossfit is the perfect way to get started. Not only does Crossfit provide a full-body workout, but it also helps to increase your cardiovascular endurance, strength, and overall fitness level. Here are five intense Crossfit workouts that will help you get in shape and get ready for summer.
1. Fran Fran Workout The Fran workout is a classic Crossfit workout that consists of 21-15-9 reps of thrusters and pull-ups.</description></item><item><title>5 Crossfit Workouts to Boost Your Endurance</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-to-boost-your-endurance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:16:56 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-to-boost-your-endurance/</guid><description>
5 Crossfit Workouts to Boost Your Endurance Do you struggle with fatigue and burnout during your Crossfit workouts? Or are you simply looking for ways to improve your endurance and overall performance in the gym?
If so, you've come to the right place. In this article, we've compiled a list of 5 Crossfit workouts that are designed specifically for boosting endurance and improving overall fitness.
1. Tabata Intervals Tabata intervals are a great way to improve your endurance and increase your overall fitness level.</description></item></channel></rss>