<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>workouts on Crossfit Workouts</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/tags/workouts/</link><description>Recent content in workouts on Crossfit Workouts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2023, Crossfit Workouts; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 20:45:40 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/tags/workouts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 CrossFit WODs to Improve Endurance</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-wods-improve-endurance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 20:45:40 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-wods-improve-endurance/</guid><description>
If you're serious about CrossFit, you know that having good endurance is key to performing well in competitions or even everyday workouts. But how do you improve your endurance?
Look no further than these 5 CrossFit WODs, designed to help you build the stamina you need to tackle any workout that comes your way.
1. &amp;quot;Annie&amp;quot; This classic CrossFit WOD is a great way to improve both cardiovascular endurance and core strength.</description></item><item><title>10 Crossfit Workouts to Build Muscle and Burn Fat</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-workouts-to-build-muscle-burn-fat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:53:46 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-workouts-to-build-muscle-burn-fat/</guid><description>
If you're looking to get in shape and build muscle while burning fat, Crossfit is the perfect workout for you. The combination of strength training and high-intensity interval training (HIIT) helps you build muscle and burn fat at the same time. Here are 10 Crossfit workouts that you can try to help you achieve your fitness goals.
1. Cindy Cindy is a classic Crossfit workout that consists of three exercises: pull-ups, push-ups, and air squats.</description></item><item><title>10 Secrets You Need to Know to Crush CrossFit</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-secrets-you-need-to-know-to-crush-crossfit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:53:46 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-secrets-you-need-to-know-to-crush-crossfit/</guid><description>
As a CrossFit enthusiast, you know that dominating your workouts requires dedication, hard work, and discipline. To take your fitness game to the next level, you need to know the top secrets that CrossFit pros use to achieve success. In this post, we will share with you 10 secrets that will help you crush your CrossFit workout routine and reach your fitness goals.
1. Train with purpose To make progress in your CrossFit workouts, you need to have a purpose.</description></item><item><title>10 CrossFit Workouts for a Full-Body Burn</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-crossfit-workouts-for-full-body-burn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:24:44 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-crossfit-workouts-for-full-body-burn/</guid><description>
Are you tired of your current workout routine and looking to switch things up? CrossFit may be just what you're looking for.
CrossFit is a high-intensity workout program that focuses on functional movements such as weightlifting, gymnastics, and cardio. These workouts target multiple muscle groups for a full-body burn that will leave you feeling strong and energized.
Here are 10 CrossFit workouts that will challenge you and help you achieve your fitness goals:</description></item><item><title>10 CrossFit Workouts for Beginners</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:24:44 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-10-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</guid><description>
If you're new to CrossFit, you may feel a little overwhelmed by the variety of workouts that are out there. The good news is that there are plenty of CrossFit workouts for beginners that will help you build strength, endurance, and confidence in a safe and effective way.
Here are 10 CrossFit workouts for beginners that you can try out today:
1. Cindy's Cousin 5 rounds for time 200m run 10 push-ups 15 air squats 20 sit-ups 2.</description></item><item><title>10 Crossfit Workouts to Get You in Shape for Summer</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/10-crossfit-workouts-for-summer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:24:44 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/10-crossfit-workouts-for-summer/</guid><description>
Are you ready for summer? If not, don't worry - we've got you covered with 10 intense Crossfit workouts that will whip you into shape and have you feeling confident on the beach.
1. &amp;quot;Cindy&amp;quot; 20-minute AMRAP (As Many Rounds As Possible) 5 pull-ups 10 push-ups 15 air squats 2. &amp;quot;Fran&amp;quot; 21-15-9 reps for time Thrusters (95 lbs for men, 65 lbs for women) Pull-ups 3. &amp;quot;Murph&amp;quot; For time 1-mile run 100 pull-ups 200 push-ups 300 air squats 1-mile run 4.</description></item><item><title>5 Crossfit Workouts for Beginners</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:24:44 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</guid><description>
Are you new to Crossfit and not sure where to begin? Don't worry, we've got you covered! Here are 5 beginner-friendly workouts to help you get started on your Crossfit journey.
1. Cindy Cindy Crossfit Workout Cindy is a classic Crossfit workout that is perfect for beginners. It consists of 5 pull-ups, 10 push-ups, and 15 air squats, repeated as many times as possible in 20 minutes. This workout is great for building endurance and strength.</description></item><item><title>5 Crossfit Workouts For Beginners That Will Get You Hooked!</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:24:44 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-5-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</guid><description>
If you're looking for a workout that will push your limits, Crossfit might just be the solution you need! Here are 5 Crossfit workouts that are perfect for beginners.
Workouts 1. Air Squats Air Squats are a great way to improve your lower body strength.
Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart. Keeping your chest up and your back straight, lower your body until your thighs are parallel to the floor. Push through your heels to return to a standing position.</description></item><item><title>10 Best Crossfit Workouts for Beginners</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-best-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:23:05 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-best-crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/</guid><description>
10 Best Crossfit Workouts for Beginners Are you new to Crossfit and wondering how to get started? With so many options available, it can be overwhelming to choose the best workouts to include in your routine. This article will outline the 10 best Crossfit workouts for beginners.
1. Air Squats Air squats are a fundamental exercise in Crossfit. They target your glutes, quads, and hamstrings. To perform an air squat, stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and slowly lower your hips down until your thighs are parallel to the ground.</description></item><item><title>5 CrossFit Workouts to Build Your Core Strength</title><link>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-workouts-core-strength/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 19:23:05 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://crossfit-workouts.github.io/post/2023-03-25-crossfit-workouts-core-strength/</guid><description>
Are you looking to build your core strength and get a toned midsection? Look no further than these 5 CrossFit workouts that are guaranteed to challenge your abs and rev up your fitness routine.
Sit-up and Press-up Circuit: This workout combines two classic moves to target both your core and upper body. Start with 20 sit-ups to work your abs, followed by 10 press-ups to target your chest and arms. Repeat for 4 sets, resting only 30 seconds between each set.</description></item></channel></rss>